{
    "subject": "Ibrahim_Nasir",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Naseema_Mohamed",
    "human_readable": "Ibrahim Nasir is married to Naseema Mohamed.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.988513171672821,
            "question": "Is Naseema Mohamed married to Ibrahim Nasir?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9866470098495483,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Ibrahim Nasir and Naseema Mohamed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9632163643836975,
            "question": "Is Ibrahim Nasir in a relationship with Naseema Mohamed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9443230032920837,
            "question": "Who is Ibrahim Nasir married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9355841279029846,
            "question": "To whom is Ibrahim Nasir currently married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9188423752784729,
            "question": "Who is Naseema Mohamed married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9052006006240845,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Ibrahim Nasir and Naseema Mohamed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8242508172988892,
            "question": "What is the name of Ibrahim Nasir's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8059351444244385,
            "question": "What is the name of Ibrahim Nasir's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7113043069839478,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marital status of Ibrahim Nasir?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ibrahim Nasir is married to Naseema Mohamed.",
            "html": "yago_4412_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Ibrahim Nasir's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_4412_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Ibrahim Nasir's wife?",
            "html": "yago_4412_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Ibrahim Nasir and Naseema Mohamed?",
            "html": "yago_4412_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4412_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4412_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4412_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4412_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4412_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4412_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4412_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4412_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4412_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4412_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Naseema Mohamed was the third wife of former President Ibrahim Nasir, and held significant positions in Maldivian history, thereby confirming their marital relationship."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}